How to make a pocket pocket strap
Tips and Tricks
Hi, everyone. This is Tips and Tricks.
Today, I will show you how to make a pocket pocket strap.
Like the pocket pocket, we also use the pocket pocket to make a pocket pocket strap.
We can see the effect of the pocket pocket strap on the pocket pocket strap.
Here is a real hole-in-the-box effect made by using duplicate simulation.
In the case of duplicate simulation, there is a mutual effect between the board and the duplicate.
Currently, duplicate simulation can only be used in CPU simulation.
So if you need to use duplicate simulation, it is recommended to switch to CPU simulation.
We can see the hole-in-the-box effect on the left side.
It is to pass a complete rope through this duplicate.
Next, we need to pass this rope on the right side through a wooden buckle.
In order to make it easier to operate, it is recommended that you first divide this rope into three parts.
You can use the hook and loop tool to divide the board.
Divide it into three parts here.
It is also to make it easier to pass through the board.
Then add a fixed pin on the divided board.
And turn on simulation.
Then add a fixed pin here.
It is to make it easier to adjust the shape of the board and the position of the moving board.
Next, add a wooden buckle.
If you already have a corresponding duplicate solution,
you can add it.
You can also find a similar component in CLOAD library or CONNECT.
Add it to the 3D window and use it.
Then here, we can copy the wooden buckle that we already have in the object window.
And drag it into the 3D window to add it.
Here, we can use the positioning ball directly.
Adjust the position of the wooden buckle through the positioning ball.
Make the top board pass through the ring in the wooden buckle.
You can see that this board has actually passed through the wooden buckle.
So you can turn on simulation.
Look at its buckle effect.
You can see that the board and the duplicate are mutually effective at this time.
The board will hang the duplicate.
Like the real buckle effect.
We need to pay attention to duplicate simulation.
The board has a conflict between the duplicate and the duplicate.
Therefore, in the process of making,
if the board and the duplicate pass through,
you can use the selection tool to adjust the board to pass through.
Prevent simulation from the conflict between the board and the duplicate.
If you see the area where there is a pass through,
you can use the selection tool to select it.
And use the positioning ball to adjust its position.
So, the upper part of the wooden buckle is done.
Then we wear the upper part of the wooden buckle.
You can adjust the remaining two parts of this strap.
Because we have increased the thickness of the board.
To make it easier to look at.
The looping effect of the wooden buckle.
You can switch to the clothing suspension type.
Switch to the texture surface.
Then here.
We can see the pass-through effect of not only the thickness of the suspension.
Let me remind you here.
If there is a deformation in the simulation process,
it can also be adjusted in the right-hand attribute editor.
Adjust its rigidity.
The larger the rigidity, the more difficult it is to deform the duplicate.
You can also adjust the thickness of the conflict.
You can adjust the size of the gap between the duplicate and the board.
Then make the looping effect of the strap.
We can arrange this small board in the position of the looping on the wooden buckle.
And adjust its position through the positioning ball.
Make it pass through the wooden buckle on one side.
You can also switch to a different angle.
Check the effect of the board.
Here we have arranged the position on one side.
We can add a inner line to it here.
Folding arrangement.
You can click on the 3D window.
Then use the internal multidirectional line tool.
Draw a inner line.
Then select the folding arrangement tool in the 3D window.
Select the inner line to fold.
Then at the bottom.
You can also add a new inner line and fold it.
Arrangement.
You can check whether there is a surface area.
If there is, you can adjust the folding angle.
At this time, the effect of this front buckle is also done.
Then we can put the other two side boards.
In the state of opening the simulation.
Use the fixed needle.
Move its board position to the part that needs to be connected together.
Got it!
Then we can remove all the pins on the board.
Ok...
Tumbing the board together.
Get ready forJa title.
Open the simulation, check the cross-section of the board and the component, and adjust the cross-section area between the board and the component by selecting the grid tool.
You can also select the cross-section area in the 2D window frame, and adjust the location of the area by locating the ball.
In this way, the effect of the cross-section of the board and the component is done.
Since the rope belt is a complete board, we need to merge these three boards together to form a complete belt.
Here you can also change the angle of these two cross-section lines to 180 degrees, or delete these two internal lines.
Finally, you can render the clothing type,
and change it to the surface of the dense pattern.
In this way, the thickness of the rope belt can also be displayed.
Let's start the simulation again.
In this way, the whole adjustment belt, the real effect of the cross-section, is also done.